{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"1158","name":"Franklin Gourmet Dairy Bar","address":"8405 Mack Ave","zipcode":"48214","owner":"Franklin, Suzette","licenseNumber":"072456","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"5/4/2018","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Seasonal","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","geom":"0101000020E6100000C4F4B71623C054C0701D4FDD322F4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"42120","establishmentid":"1158","name":"Franklin Gourmet Dairy Bar","inspectionDate":"2018-05-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"42120","inspectionDate":"5/8/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1158","name":"Franklin Gourmet Dairy Bar","violationCode":"3-304.14","violationDescription":"(A)  Cloths that are in use for wiping FOOD spills on TABLEWARE shall be maintained dry and used for no other purpose. \r\n(B)  Cloths in-use for wiping counters and equipment shall be held between uses in   a chemical sanitizer solution, and laundered daily.\r\n(C)  Cloths in-use for wiping surfaces in contact with raw animal FOODS shall be      kept separate from cloths used for other purposes.\r\n(D)  Dry wiping cloths and the chemical sanitizing solutions shall be free of FOOD    debris or visible soil.\r\n(E)  Containers of chemical sanitizing solutions shall be stored off the floor and         used in a manner that prevents contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, SINGLE-SERVICE, or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n(E)  SINGLE-USE disposable sanitizer wipes shall be used in accordance lable               instructions.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Wiping cloth(s)","subItem":"wet","problemDescription":"Stored soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"Inside the Ice cream freezer","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"42120","inspectionDate":"5/8/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1158","name":"Franklin Gourmet Dairy Bar","violationCode":"6-202.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise approved, light bulbs shall be shielded, coated, or otherwise shatter-resistant in areas where there is exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Light shielding","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FOOD SERVICE AREA","subLocation":"Missing Light Shield(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide adequate light shields and end caps or shatter-proof bulbs."}]},{"inspectionid":"38720","establishmentid":"1158","name":"Franklin Gourmet Dairy Bar","inspectionDate":"2017-05-16T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"1","pfcount":"0","ccount":"7","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"7","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"38720","inspectionDate":"5/16/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1158","name":"Franklin Gourmet Dairy Bar","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FOOD PREP LINE","subLocation":"At the Grease extraction filters","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"38720","inspectionDate":"5/16/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1158","name":"Franklin Gourmet Dairy Bar","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"At the Floor","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"38720","inspectionDate":"5/16/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1158","name":"Franklin Gourmet Dairy Bar","violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All of the following food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American national standards institute, utilizing the conference for food protection standards:  (a) A food service establishment that is not any of the following:    (i) Operating under a temporary food service establishment license.  (ii) A vending machine location.     (b) An extended retail food establishment.  (c) Operated within a retail grocery.  (2) An individual certified under subsection (1) shall be recognized with full faith and credit by the state and all local units of government throughout the state.  (3) The department may promulgate rules to do all of the following:  (a) Develop requirements for retail food establishments to follow when employing certified food safety managers or personnel.  (b) Set a reasonable date for compliance with the requirements under subdivision (a) taking into consideration existing local personnel certification requirements.  (c) Establish certification fees necessary to implement, maintain, and track certified individuals directly or by contract. The department may annually adjust the schedule of fees to provide that the fee charged is sufficient to cover the cost of the certification tracking program.  (d) Implement and enforce the requirements described in subdivision (a).    (4) The certification program developed by the American national standards institute, as it exists on April 1, 2008 , is incorporated by reference. The department may adopt updates to the certification program accreditation standards in subsection (1) by rule.     (5) This section does not prohibit any local legislative body from implementing a food handler program, an employee health certification program, or a manager certification program, if it is not in conflict with this section.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"ICE CREAM PALOR","subLocation":"At the PERSON IN CHARGE","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"38720","inspectionDate":"5/16/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1158","name":"Franklin Gourmet Dairy Bar","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"REAR STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"Inside the Refrigerator/freezers","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"38720","inspectionDate":"5/16/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1158","name":"Franklin Gourmet Dairy Bar","violationCode":"5-501.17","violationDescription":"A toilet room used by females shall be provided with a covered receptacle for sanitary napkins.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Covered waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"Missing Covered waste container","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"38720","inspectionDate":"5/16/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1158","name":"Franklin Gourmet Dairy Bar","violationCode":"6-202.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise approved, light bulbs shall be shielded, coated, or otherwise shatter-resistant in areas where there is exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Light shielding","subItem":"light shield(s)","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"ICE CREAM PALOR","subLocation":"Missing Light Shield(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"38720","inspectionDate":"5/16/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1158","name":"Franklin Gourmet Dairy Bar","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"wall(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"Cracked","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Wall (North)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"38720","inspectionDate":"5/16/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1158","name":"Franklin Gourmet Dairy Bar","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"water line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Sink","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"36349","establishmentid":"1158","name":"Franklin Gourmet Dairy Bar","inspectionDate":"2016-09-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"1","pfcount":"2","ccount":"4","criticalcount":"3","noncritical":"4","correctedcritical":"3","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"36349","inspectionDate":"9/7/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1158","name":"Franklin Gourmet Dairy Bar","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"At the WALK-IN COOLER","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-09-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"36349","inspectionDate":"9/7/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1158","name":"Franklin Gourmet Dairy Bar","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the FILTERS","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"36349","inspectionDate":"9/7/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1158","name":"Franklin Gourmet Dairy Bar","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"chlorine","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"ICE CREAM PALOR","subLocation":"Missing Test strips","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-09-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"36349","inspectionDate":"9/7/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1158","name":"Franklin Gourmet Dairy Bar","violationCode":"7-204.11","violationDescription":"Chemical SANITIZERS and other chemical antimicrobials applied to FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall meet the requirements specified in this code. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not comply with law","subProblem":"","location":"ICE CREAM PALOR","subLocation":"At the Bleach","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-09-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide labels that comply with law."},{"inspectionid":"36349","inspectionDate":"9/7/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1158","name":"Franklin Gourmet Dairy Bar","violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \r\n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not available","subProblem":"","location":"ICE CREAM PALOR","subLocation":"No Food thermometer(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-09-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Make available at all times."},{"inspectionid":"36349","inspectionDate":"9/7/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1158","name":"Franklin Gourmet Dairy Bar","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"ICE CREAM PALOR","subLocation":"Inside the Refrigerator/freezers","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"36349","inspectionDate":"9/7/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1158","name":"Franklin Gourmet Dairy Bar","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"water line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"ICE CREAM PALOR","subLocation":"Across from the  Sink (2 compartment)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"1158"}}